JAAN SANGHA

www.jaansangha.com | jaansangha10@gmail.com | 289-500-5226 | Toronto, ON.

GAME PROGRAMMER

Knowledgeable and detail-oriented entry level Game Programmer with experience working in a fast-paced environment. Solid familiarity gained in developing video games through various projects and 3-year program taken with George Brown. Highly developed technical and analytical skills with experience in working as part of an efficient and goal-oriented team. Strong communication skills with ability to resolve problems with calm and professional demeanour.

Technical Proficiency:

• Languages: C++, C#, Java, C, Swift, Python, JavaScript

• Other: Unity, Unreal Engine 4, HTML 5, CSS, Git, Trello, Perforce

EDUCATION

Ontario College Advanced Diploma: Game Programming

George Brown College Toronto, ON

Major Units of Study: Advanced programming, Artificial Intelligence, Mathematics, Data Structures and Algorithms, Game Physics, 3D Graphics Programming, Game Engines, Game production, Console Game Development, Multiplayer Systems, Mobile Game Development etc.

RELATED PROJECTS

Cardemon September 2022 - Current

• Currently working on a turn based combat game that has many popular RPG elements like; card collecting, melee combat, farming, crafting.

• Built With: Unity, C#

Roly Controly February 2023 - Current

- Currently working on a mobile game where the player uses their device accelerometer to move the ball around and complete different levels.
- The game is expected to be released this summer on the Play Store.
- Built With: Unity, C#

CAR ARENA GAME

September 2020 – December 2020

Graduated April 2022

- Built an arena style game where the player takes control of a car and must traverse the map and destroy all the turrets before they get destroyed. Collaborated with another developer to create the game physics from scratch, without any pre-set physics.
- Built With: Unreal Engine 4, C++

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Game DeveloperNibbit.ai

March 2023 - Current
Toronto, ON

- Brainstorm and design mini game concepts and elements by coordinating with the design team
- Develop frameworks and translate design ideas into clean and efficient code by deploying game engine
- Test game features and ensure bug free releases

IOS SUPPORT ADVISOR

May 2022 - September 2022

Apple (Contract)

Toronto, ON

- Identify and solve complex technical problems with work-issued programs based on customer feedback and needs
- Develop a strong knowledge of Apple products in order to provide accurate and efficient support to all customers
- Used CRM technology to log and provide accurate solutions to all customers